{
    "id": "66a0f363ec694fb7be3e0ca125c54e38",
    "title": "Because And Because Of",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We cancelled the trip ………………….. the rain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f003e2ba9cae4065bbf1c51ef1c369a5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I helped him ………………… I liked him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "705c4f0d54b04bed998b6f8786b58afb"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was all ……………….. my mother that I reached where I am today.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d171552474a44675b42e65a589f1da5c"
        },
        {
            "question": "You have to hurry up ………………… you are already late.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1215b36be20f40f6a600a2506acfc0f8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was late …………………. my car broke down on the way home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9ec10d73000d41729d4c42ff986b7583"
        },
        {
            "question": "She worked hard ……………….. she wanted to pass.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "044ae9dce21144d28b4c51fc15cee6b3"
        },
        {
            "question": "I sat down to rest ………………… I was tired.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2827052dcf834e0aa70a89cf2e24c6fb"
        },
        {
            "question": "She didn’t get the job ………………. she didn’t apply in time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "44a0cdf3597a4107ba779ff702727056"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………….. his strange accent, people assume that he is a foreigner.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Because",
                "Because of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "86e7a6077f84462e93dcafb4b14da5c0"
        },
        {
            "question": "He lost his job ………………… his drug problem.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b6c599a564004384aa8c1612adcd3ffa"
        }
    ]
}